Ima, he's the reason
why I lost my job!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[IMA] It was you?
You bastard! You're the reason
my daughter is worn out!
Are you sure
she's related to Don Nato?
Maybe you can check it again.
She scammed me once.
- Me?
- Right?
You used my tocino (cured pork)
for a free promo.
[SCOFFS]
"His tocino."
Hey.
You really are shameless.
You had the nerve
to say "my tocino".
Do you even own
that tocino brand?
You own...
Pindang Tocino?
Will they be living here?
[ZIA] Of course.
Once you get married.
- No!
- [SILLY SFX PLAYING]
I'm not going to
marry a scammer.
Hey, watch it!
You're so full of yourself!
Don't marry that man.
Who does he think he is?
[JUNE] You think you're cute?
[JUNE] Will I be living
in a house full of pork now?
Is it 'Bye sparkling lights
of the city
and back to lonely dark nights'?
You have to convince Ping, June.
Because if Don Nato's will
falls through,
all his estate and assets
will go to his foundation.
Dear, you know what,
you don't have to do this.
Let's go home.
We can always earn that money.
We're hardworking, remember?
Don't do this. Come on.
Ima.
No matter how much hard work
we put into day and night,
I don't think
we can ever afford a house.
This is a sure win.
Game, Attorney.
We'll stay here.
I'll make sure
Papa Ping falls in love with me.
[IMA] Hold up.
I didn't like the sound of that.
Men should be the ones
courting the women.
[JUNE] Ima!
It's different now.
All genders are equal.
And besides...
Miss Judith is coming.
[SILLY SFX PLAYING]
[WHISPERS] Judith who?
[WHISPERS]
Judith, due date. The bills.
We have to do
what's best right now.
Alright.
[JUNE] Wait up!
[BODY THUDS]
I'll not get down
until you get out of this car!
I might throw up
but I'll keep fighting!
[TAPS LOUDLY] Get out!
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]